Collectors, and so I will follow this
with the rights of homework, but most likely I will get
distracted and talk about something too
long. Maybe we won't even
finish the first lesson today, but let's
try. So I called the first course and it's
funny, the flag and two teacher trainings. I
will share with you the infection of what was
happening while I described this
course, what I was thinking about, what was happening at that
time. If I remember the
first course is called the three main
teachings of Buddhism. Tell the lama with us,
females, this is the lunar short name. Here's a
longer version of this. We break it down.
Yesterday, I taught Masha a new word from pit,
and yesterday I taught American food and
business.
This means one thing that
annoys me most is people who
mispronounce the
main teachings of Buddhism. So if you
want to fail in the
teacher training, just bring it
incorrectly. Let's talk. Principal
in English means the main thing. The
main teaching will be the
principle in English in Russian. Reception
as a district. The main main
teaching of Buddhism means the main teaching, what does the main thing mean?
Sang everything so
main.  An idea such as the principle
of gravity is the main thing and therefore do not
call it anything else, do not do this,
I have seen many teachers do this,
we are talking about the main teachings of Buddhism,
some people cited this
incorrectly, they called it the three principles,
they simply do not understand that the Tibetan
word should comes after lama, kids are
means this does not mean principle along the way,
this is incorrect and many people translate it this way
if you see a book with such on the edge,
just pull and supply how many two of
these I threw out, therefore, unfortunately, the word
which means the main one
always appears after the noun,
that is, it is like a red book, they are a
red book,
sometimes an adjective comes after the
noun and in Russian we
also say this, that is, it is like a
red book instead of saying the
red book and
this confuses many people, in general, do not
call it the principles of the teaching, call
it the main evenings, the three main paths
is the real name of this course, I
changed the name of the course to make it
more accessible, snow,
our variable book became dig on the
cover called the main teachings of
Buddhism, it is not called the three main
paths,
I was the name to make
this book more accessible, available and I
put this photo of the statue on  On
the cover of this book, it's sold at a 10.
This is a real image. The rating for this is the
only one. It was a real statue
now. He has a big nose and big
eyes. This is what he looks like. His enemy
called him Mr. Big Nose. He
really had a big nose. His face was
very strong. So this is a real
image. This is a statue. It was destroyed
during the Cultural Revolution and they put up
another one where he is all beautiful and cute.
This is unreal. This is why this image is
black and white because the photograph
was taken in the
1930s. So the first course is based
on the main teachings of Buddhism,
which are also called the three main
paths. Now it's the path of lamps in Teletskogo,
like Sanskrit. A muzzle in this case
doesn't mean a
road. It doesn't mean a method. This doesn't
mean a method. And in teaching, the
correct parameters are the second topic
or subject. A path is a synonym for
understanding or awareness. That is, it's
mental.
They tell me about three methods in Buddhism.
We don't even talk about three paths
that can be taken. We talk about
three
relationships. This is very important. If you don't
understand this, you don't understand the whole course. We don't
talk about three methods. We don't talk
about three roads.  We are talking about three
attitudes
that are the main teachings of
people in Buddhism. We are not talking about books,
we are talking about the idea. Three big ideas. This is
what you should know. The
author of this book is part of the song of ours.
By the way, it means lord, that is, it is a
respectful and respectful address to
klaus, and in Chinese, such a respectful
and respectful
name is jen. For example, a diamond in
Tibetan is called / george, which
means king of stones. Yes, this is a stone. J
is a lie. A respectful address, therefore,
jackson cup means almost guilt, and to those
whom you can simply call him
castle po, but it is a little impolite if
you covenant him, and now he hooves
more. Sometimes we get excited, we call him neck
rinpoche, which means valuable lord, it is like a
jewel. A very respectful
address. If someone talks about
jerren, be they saying protsenko po, you
can use this, as if
simply center. Many people pronounce his
name with
song hope, this is incorrect, it is peb pec.
They confuse transliteration with sound.
When you take foreign words and
pronounce them in English, you write
how it is pronounced. You  Don't try to understand
how it's written in the original language of
Gene, otherwise you'll have Sri Lanka or
Sego Nanda, both of which are incorrect. This is
incorrect, this is an incorrect
transcription, this is not a sound, this is harmful.
This is a strange error. If you see a letter that says "k" (I ca
n't) and "shans" (
hanka), this is incorrect,
throw it out.
Protect the one who wrote it. I don't understand the
difference between tractor, plaster,
and pronunciation. It's like from 1 clip
for Moscow. Moscow, Moscow, and
this is a transcription.
We pronounce "grin" in English. Don't
write down foreign words for countries, as
they're written, write down how they're
pronounced. They
wrote my lava's name incorrectly at the passport agency.
They would have seen "te
h" in the transcription. They wrote it incorrectly.
It's terrible to change someone's name "
koyuki" because you can't tell the difference.
What's the difference between letters and sounds? You'll
never do that or I'll get
angry.
Now his name is "monastic" and I'm going
through homework. Say "lob" (San-Tropez) "tracta
lapsa
chappa" (lob).  Sapsan means pure,
itself means a pure forehead, san4
sum te in Sanskrit
and the
last name is the word you have no
fights in Sanskrit kirte as in darma
kirte chandra kirte kirte means
famous everyone listened to him he is incredible
very popular that is his name means
super famous pure mind
this is his monastic name you take
when creating the name of a monastic take and the
first name from the monk who took the vow and
manarsky and spoiler
if they are a monk, for example, Mike, that all
monks who became monks at 4 years old will
receive the name Mycroft half of the
monks in the monastery have the name jumpa this is
very confusing my monastic name the first
word lapsa is the name of my teacher teacher
[music]
the second what is the name of the taiga with this work
and these are the three main paths the third question we
go to homework
[music]
inksystem monsters birther we run around
connected and vacuum cleaner Christian tradition
there is a lot of attention on and close you what is it we do
not stand for what many of this
has become classics  Jabbu
is described in general. Pistol means a
secret important letter. This book has 14
verses. This letter was written to a
student by means of
which the student wrote. His name was Gondwana. Drac
Po was in love with checks and hope. From the very
beginning, there are many peace
drawings where he is depicted sitting at his
feet and mountains and Stubb that rocks are rated
go east
for 5 build 108 monastery that he
was not 11 or lazy students. He did what
the teacher told him although he did not
want to go this is the last thing he
wanted to do. Leaving the
teacher Tsongkhapa said go do
n't come back until you build 108 and
he did it. He went east colors
built 183.
Guess what the name of the last one is - for
so Hudson trample yes, that means now the
treasurer himself to us I completed it I did the
last monastery and it was called full
completely completed and it is a famous
monastery I knew about the hotel and this
book still exists there. This letter
was written to this student who
went to the east of Tibet and  I was upset and
Jackson K is trying to say in this letter, well, okay, don't be
upset, I'll write you a review now
for only $50. I'm not saying
you're interested in money, well, not for
free, but I have more fun this way. Honestly, I'm
so simple, without years, ready for 17 basic
and 7 courses. There's another important letter
that was sent to Havana. Yes, why does the
letter say that I, and
I was the person who wrote with a
spear gesture, not only to build a
monastery,
but also monks, but into monks, people. He didn't
fully answer. He said he was a
student. I remember I want to meditate. This is
here. 7. And this is not in the face, not in the legs, not
inhalation, this is not the topic. Did
you respect the peace of people last
week or did you irritate other people? In mind,
this is incredible. Letters and buffers. And
by the way, at 10 we cost, we give a chapter, what is the
third stage? We sell meditation hour
by hour. At the end, we talk and all this is not
important and that is not important. What you hear in
myself comes from how you
treated last week, it doesn't matter.
Which left leg is up? Does the control
exhale? Are you long enough? It doesn't matter.
Forget about it if you want
it to be a good meditation. Don't
upset other people.
Be mindful so as not to upset
other people. Be kind.
Speak softly to other people.
Be attentive to how they
feel. What is their facial expression?
If it's so unpleasant. A woman in labor, then
stop because you are sowing seeds to
hear bad thoughts in
your mind. I am in meditation and your meditation is in
place. At this moment, everything happens from
what is done. They irritate other
people.
He had a nickname. Tell me, while he is a
bomb, so cool. Sako. A cabinet of combat food. You are a
master of their steel. Here is the wrong
answer. The one in the answers here
pronounces his name incorrectly. It needs to be
corrected. It's a bomb, some region
where he is from. Kansas. A district and region is a
word for a local priest.
Small lighting. A small local
priest. Sometimes you can see it
just like that. I put it here. It seems he
lived during the same years as Tanka. I am
trying to provide as much information as possible.
Insert a comment here.
The one you are studying was written by whom. The
entire translation is a translation.  The entire
comment is in the course of reading I
remember how when I brought it, I was on
retreat for 1 month near the Grand Canyon.
I remember translating these dates on
the bank 878, I
didn't hear you 1941, he was one of the
most famous teachers of the
zinc tradition, the clock cops, you know that
he was number one, I'll tell you a little
about him,
his grains, and you can read about it in the
book, in the book,
agar might, I wrote about my teacher,
canarem, bunch of his, lob, santor, china.
Sorry, I asked him to tell me a
story about the park.
It was hard because he didn't
like answering my questions. I
offered to drive him to Washington every month for
5 hours. He had nowhere to get out
of the car. And by the way, they managed to get him. Miller
collapsed, and he was raised by stars. He became
Lego's chief assistant. He became a nanny
for all the monasteries. There is
only one copy of Lema in the college. They found it in
Russia, St. Petersburg. It says there
are 20 houses and
12 colleges. 3 colleges have
cheese inside.  Monstera girl on Sara
JD are not so
educated from this is super cool between
these two there is a green line from an
invisible green Lydia which you do not
cross otherwise something will happen you have
no idea what happened but isn't it
impossible to cross and don't like the Messerschmitts you
know very cool
many cool ones including don't tell anyone
in general how do my students feel about
the college the structure of all the great
monasteries of Tsongkhapa
there is also local kindness when I went
I was in Princeton we had an Arizona club
and all the students from the Arizona club we all
drank beer together and at the monastery there are
such as there were different houses and in the
very east the language is such a very
strange not even quite Tibetan in any
case for some reason my teacher was
placed in a belong house at the age of 7 or
5 before Islam above the lama in the history of
our our house column stage bomb
window frame he is from your code g so you
must be loyal firm
he is from our college you understand it is a
great honor to be
from his colleges at home I had the honor to
conduct debates  с третьим по музыке
он проводил их экзамен на его геродота
за годы того как я провалюсь икса и
традиция вот в этом поле доме это
геофизика нужна
winner of защищаться тебе нужно
защищаться сначала в своем колледже
перед тем как ты защищаешься в монастырь
и он защищался в нашем колледже нас там
было всего 50 ма на вопрос но человек
который первый атаковал его старше
студент который еще нигерша быть людьми
и это был я я атаковала первыми тропинка
бога и я атакую ​​побоку на дебатах
это была моя рабочим угадайте какой
вопрос я задал после того как вы
становитесь просветленным ног или
становитесь буду как вы можете помогать
страдающим существам потому что вас нет
вас же нету семян видеть их страдающий
страдающими эти существа вы видите их
всех самыми высшими бодхисаттва мы в раю
как вы можете помочь страдающего
перестановок становитесь
будай чуть больше не видите страдания
как будто нападал
и когда оппонент такой выше рим патча вы
просто какой-то шмок мастер дебаты
а он восстановит скажет полосу что
означает хорошо следующий
грани не я же  I did it, you did it, he
said,
we went to call the back of the courtyard and
continued the debate there for three or four hours, it
was cool, and the abbot of the
Doric College was solemn,
well, we have hair or give out, in general,
this is Pierre, according to the bank, Rinpoche, he has a
nickname in your rnykh or nickname
Gref, you in the secret teachings, we don’t
call him by the mangroves, why do our children have
him, the liver is
eternal, it means bliss, which is
associated with the vision of emptiness in
tantra, great bliss, ninka po
means chen chen chen heart heart
just heart heart bliss, this is his
secret, you will hear, so they call him in
the evenings, he was a great teacher of his
time, he graduated from our monastery,
Sara, we are from college,
but he was not the highest, Yasha, he was not the
mayor, 1st to 3rd degree holds the same as me,
if you want to be second level, you still have
four years to squeeze out, and to become the highest,
it’s another ten years, you had to wait, I’m
too old, probably much more, more
exams, but it’s interesting that he
also dared the third degree  Gish, he
wasn't the highest, they hung up beats and insane, he
did something strange, he started
teaching ordinary leaders and
it was very unusual,
buy and 10 ordinary people, not monks,
began to come to his classes, then 20
people, thirty people, by the time
he began teaching Lam-rim,
which we are studying, there were already thousands of
people and he became famous for
teaching ordinary people. He was 10 and in his
time and the songs of his time, he was
very criticized for this, very-very
strong, you say, it was a very
serious thing, they could kill for it in those
days, he was on
you will see two photographs of him. The first is a
young, handsome guy, and five
years later he looks terrible,
as if someone beat him up. They say that he was
attacked on the palette. He had a
war with spirits,
like, this war lasted a whole year and
she suffered physically. He
could never cope. If you look
at these two photographs, he is very interested in
the system, this is such a story about him. His, so
he usually came to monasteries and taught
Lam-rim,
this is also yes, you and I are studying.  During
the month, it may be from fawn. By the way, this is
how Kesha receives teachings. You
receive them because lamas
come and really give additional
subjects. This is not part of
the program. It's like a dessert. That
is, they cancel all
other classes for a month. And some tall,
tall lama comes. We embroidered and
became a Boeing. They invite all the
local people. Classes are what
happens in the morning when you study yourself.
We study during measurements in the work zone. And there is still a person who
appoints a person according to the workload. The
monastery kitchen, for example, in the monastery itself, we
all needed to listen in the kitchen every
two weeks. We had to spend
two days for two weeks. When you wash a pot, you
need a ladder to climb to the top of
this pot, then down again and wash it. This is how
this tea is for three thousand
people.
The pot is a creation. This seal is the
type who
pours tea for those who study lambre. These are
thousands of ordinary people for this position.
Choosing Shaolin books, too busy
mind my Excel. They choose these Kesha. They
can just study. Good candidates
for keep them and you.  They are not to be disturbed and they do
not need to work with other people May
Mom is a deception lamp was Kamenkov by
means of a bad boy never just
all sorts of tricks were carried out in the film
you know people do not wear in rooms people
wear
shoes inside and he some that did not leave on the
floor so that people step on them Hindus
panda panda tell me what does a
small piece of a flowey
flower mean you create such a flower from
such flowers such balls when you
are in prayers at prayers there are three
thousand people that's how they wash down 2 paw
shoots a distance of 3 meters hits
he was the best shooter he did not study
so he was stuck in the position was not needed
gray snack cook
and he makes a fragment came to visit
check the kitchen check snacks for
teaching you saw my teacher and
approached him and put his hands on his head and
said this van this one is
special this one is special and then
turned and left and something strange
then happened to my teacher he is
generally his this is some kind of he received
consciousness or spirit from this scum part
he changed completely but offered a
very important position mom very  good
money set big screen for the rest of your
life you can just drink tea and receive
offerings and he said no he said
the teacher himself no I won't go there you
idiot what will you be rich with breasts for the rest of your life
this is a good thing I want to
be only critical
I will be number one g.sh.
When you become number one, where is number one? I
put Tsongkhapa's electron urinates, got
angry, and she worked very hard to
become number one. Only in his year was there a
competition for everyone to be number one on foot, and he
won them all. He became number one among
20,000 monks during debates.
Try to win any of them.
If he says the sky isn't blue, he
can prove it. Don't even try to be a
slave. It
means special solitude. Like retreats at the
center behind the monastery, sir, yes, you can
walk there.
Like, diamond mountains, this river center,
and this retreat center was called, it
was called according to blogs, and therefore its time is a
selection,
but it wasn't a breakdown. They decided that he
would be the reincarnation of the abbot. Boom, while
he wasn't there, so what's the story? In
fact, he realized how the reincarnation of Chang
Torji is a very famous lama of the
emperor. There's still a temple in Beijing.
I saw him, which is dedicated to this one, and the
machines
are a very famous teacher of the king of
China.
You can still see him from the hotel if you go up to the 20th floor
because there are all around.  other
buildings and it's really cool time he
was very friendly with China and
really and he managed to be
friends with them with the Chinese and holes in the year
when pubam was born there was a lot of
tension and people were afraid to call him by his
real name Chang they called him
on the sides they gave another name because there were
so many political his
year this chunky
1717 mister here for 1 dollar I
study all schools
sedan you like what you went through yesterday
year he wrote the largest book in the
last now debt to be fragment
workers he had a special student
who recorded all his teachings this was
in the days when there were no iPhones and
[music]
you could record sounds people
recorded made notes like
crazy Mike Fala magician without a
microphone just taught thousands of
people and you had to have a very loud
voice and his student was you high La
Motte Richa
1901 to 1981 loops Changar [ __ ]
final the highest cash in his time and
taught  The Dalai Lama, that is, he was the
Dalai Lama's teacher, and he was an incredibly
kind person, a wonderful teacher, and
great tea, and why do we have
this book, The Gift of Liberation, which we
study? Because he spent 12 years
correcting all these notes. It
seems to me that this is the greatest book
written in Tibetan. It is the most
pleasant Tibetan language that has
ever been written. The book is perfect and
absolutely perfect. Tibetan is ideal
these days, and during the Cultural Revolution,
the level of the Tibetan language is low. I
called recently. Many years ago, I
called the monastery. No one can
speak such Tibetan.
I believe that this will be the greatest
book ever written in the Teletsky
language. 34 patches were my
teacher. My teacher, then you are his. His great-
grandchildren. This is a good line of transmission.
The person who wrote the introduction to this
work is still Olympus. The focus of complaints is San Torchin,
1921 to 2004. He taught me for
free for 30 years. I lived with him for
25 years. It was hard. He was a
difficult person. I never met him.  It was
impossible to choose a debate with him, he will
never say he did anything
right, and when I passed the exam, I got a gisher, the
first
gersh from the West in the last 600 years, but
his nephew was his close student,
and I am glad to say that he will visit us
this week. He is very old, now he is
about 80 years old, he agreed to come, the
plane landed, I asked him to give a
teaching about cinema, m p h is your grandfather, and
just tell us about his personal life,
some interesting stories, Veshav O-tar,
his name is he does not have you, he is not the
greatest scholar, moments in Niger, but he
tells stories very well, he is the
best at this, he became a master of 9 debates
in the most,
this is as an assistant abbot, assistant to the
director of the monastery, so he achieved
this position, he helped me survive,
just years
without him, I would not have survived, I was the
only foreigner who
survived there only because he was like that,
they did not believe
you, this is my entire career in the
monastery,
thanks to him, he taught me how to
wear robes, he taught me everything, trained
me for the exam  Gersh is practically like
men getting married, how to dress for the
Gersh exam. These are three levels of some
historical clothing, so you should
be grateful to him. You need to create
some kind of good relationship, red
envelopes, and he needs to be respected.
Without him, I wouldn't be here. I
learned Tibetan because he never
stops talking all the time, and
maybe I was lucky. We lived together for
about 10 years, so you'll get a good union. A
great story. I don't think
he can come now. I think these are
special Shabbat days. When you arrive, he's
here on Wednesday and will arrive on Thursday. Saturday
morning. He will give us a lecture.
Come on, everyone. Now, the text doesn't
jump straight to the three main paths.
It begins with preparatory
activities. This is such a tradition.
One of these activities is the most
traditional thing. Good luck. You say
at the beginning when you listen to these
teachings.
Avoid the three problems of the pot. We
went through this in the 700s. They
said wire 5. Idea: three problems of a
pot or vessel. Well, for $1,
tell me one of the three problems of the vessel.
If  You'll hang it up like that, the problem
will be dirty inside, yes, you can't pour
water into a dirty cup, what does this mean? Are
you mixing teaching with all sorts of other
things? Let's have two more gases, like the
other two, yes, you won't, like
the cup that has a hole, not everything flows out of you. Do
we have one? I'm asking a question, and
what else are you talking about?
The teacher is trying to pour you before the inverted cup, but you're
already filled with other ideas. You've already
gone to some shaman and performed a
ceremony with his affection. You're not open to
these days. You're already doing some strange
things. I had a student from
Ireland who actually
translated the mandala into
what's called a devil. The Celts
were very good students. She
went to the ceremony with her affection and
said, "I'll record a video," and they
gave her too much, near the dose, she
died, and all of this is on the video, so it's a
stupid idea. You understand, don't
fill yourself with stupid quotes about
spiritual real things. You can
talk to her father, who
leads our Irish group. This is  A
very sad story in any case, don't
be the first. Three things before the
teachings begin: be open. I'm something of a
scientist. I'll be open. This is not what
I'm used to, but I'll be open. It's like the
yoga classes that
the teacher said in the morning, just be
open. I'll do things you have
n't done yet. 1. 1 cup, 1 vessel, 2.
Do not mix with other things. As
a teacher, say,
if you mix with other
things, other than me, I'll throw you out in
five minutes. If you just say, "Glory to
Ascona!" and the hosts of the classes, I'll throw you out right away. You
understand.
Also, tell them you teach essays. Does
this mean you can't. The
next day, I endured that the other one, no, I'm
not like that. I understand everyone in the room
has their own traditions. Maybe you're
from a Christian or
Muslim tradition. Maybe you'll be
teaching in a Muslim country.
Then say some good things about
Muslims, and that's okay, but you shouldn't
do that. Don't
mix. [ __ ], Arsen Kursk, this is a course, and
yourself. This is a formula for
enlightenment.
If you add ayahuasca here, it
won't work, and people will be  suffer for
many millions of years, so I ask,
no, I don't ask, I demand, I order, I
mix with other things, don't smash them,
you'll sit down and that doesn't mean you can't do something, you
want to teach something else,
do something else, and another time on the Dnieper,
submit it on time, and this lesson is I
ask, no, I'm kidding, I'll take away your
certification if I find out that you are
mixing it with something else, this is a formula, it
works, I can confirm to you,
these incredible things happened to me, no
one in the world changed, you can say that
people tried it,
I'm just laughing, what are you talking about? If you
follow this correctly, you can
see the entire universe, meditation, you can
meet every living creature,
billions of creatures,
no need to tell me the rule, I'm
not interested in this, yes, I was walking, but I'm not
interested in anything else, I already
have a
Model X, no need to try to sell a
Volkswagen, well, I didn't, I really
tried it in systems, it works, I
got what I wanted, and I told you, and
this can also be done, but only if you
don't mix it with something else,
you will destroy people from if  Mix, Misha, you will
mix, you
understand, it's not because other
traditions are bad, it's just that you don't
mix the recipe for mapo tofu with a
chocolate cake. One is spicy, the other is
sweet. Mapo tofu is good, and chocolate
cake is good for nominal mixing.
You need to try making one
once, let everyone try it. Well,
let's try it tomorrow during
sports classes so that people remember that I will make you
all sick with chocolate cake.
Maybe I'll do it myself so that you
remember this. Remember it. Lama, Grandfather
Geshe Michael. Put those times, he made
us eat chocolate cake with mapo tofu. It
was terrible, so please don't
mix it. You'll
make a cake. Well, come on, no, it looks like
Norbert needs to be taught.
Well, all the texts are either divided into
three large divisions. The teaching is all
the steps 1 from 1 to the last until you
achieve enlightenment. This has three
divisions. Three divisions
depend on the motivation of the person sitting
in class.
Yagudin taught a bunch of things. The report was PayPal. These are
small people,
medium people, and big fish.
Literally, it means small people,
medium people, and big fish.  People often face it,
it's just a difference in motivation. Who will
tell me the motivation of little pink ones?
Ported
means what time you don't relate to
your height.
I'm in a halo where I don't want to go to the moon. They
went lower, outgrown,
I don't want to be born as an animal in the waters or
spirit armor. I don't want the most tender
rebirth. This is the motivation of little
battleships. I spend money too quickly, yes,
shape,
how it runs for thousands of dollars, well,
thousands, thousands of bucks later, from the data of
life.
Truth is, what one teaching hung, which was satisfied the young little man, what they want, and you owe me a thousand. I'm already in queens, everything is canceled. Phew, before captivity, pen, pen, poll, a person who understands the pen, teachings about the pen correctly, wine, year, cannot
get to the lower rebirth, this is
impossible. You are destroying all the seeds in
your being that you sent vases,
regime for citizens. Can you imagine? People also
complain that I teach too often.
Pen anime, later they will thank you if you
understand the pen correctly, that is,
the master knew about the path of
preparation, this is a deep understanding of the pen
and actually hold leader points. If
you understand this, this is not  you'll get to
lower rebirths, cool, so
forget about little people, that would be too much,
and what is an average person?
I don't want any samsara at all. I don't
want any suffering. It's important
if I become president or become a
janitor. It's all the same suffering. I do
n't want that. I want nirvana for me. The
big big person wants them. They want
everyone to be enlightened. These are the three
big divisions of the Lavra teachings.
Okay, so let's get started.
5 minutes until the brooch. You're the ones with me. I still have a
few minutes. I think I'll have time. 9 questions.
Name three fundamental ones. It would be
mute. The three main paths. It's called
renunciation. This is a big word in English.
Nobody uses this word in Russian anymore.
When we decide to use the word "renunciation," our team
of translators
uses the word "renunciation." Or, I send Alison to a
Mexican restaurant and I say, "Tell
the waiter what renunciation means."
Tell him, I don't know English very
well. What does renunciation mean? He
won't answer the waiter. What renunciation means?
Don't use it,
but I used it.
20 years ago, this word was potash, and that's how it was
taught to me, and it's not the best
translation. No better.  Renunciation follow
me obeys the letters we have a little
content now
renunciation upsets I will not drive a
fancy car I will not have much
money I will eat only rice and bananas
vegetables I will live an earthly life I
will not dress in nice clothes and so
once the classical meaning of renunciation and
this is not what we want this is not what
we want you to do we both
already said yesterday if you practice Buddhism in
the right way you will be successful whether you
want to be successful or not you can
run away but money will run after you I
apologize and you will be famous you
will have clothes cars they all all this will
run after you you will not be able to
avoid this your own if you understand the seeds and
you sow it you only need to serve
other people you will be super successful how much how
many Habibi
Asanga teachers were princes of
OSAGO and quieter there everyone was objects the world
this does not mean that you need to run away from the
cars of girlfriends and so on this does not
mean it means that if you do not
understand the system of seeds everything around you
uremia will end and die including you
If you don't understand this, there are more seeds
to lead, the seeds haven't run out,
good ones, yes, you will die and you wouldn't have
money, you won't have a partner, any
happiness is replaceable, it doesn't mean you
can't have happiness, love or a partner
is not renunciation, I tried going to a cave,
I spent a month, it's not the best, I had a
green snake that could die from its
bite, where the stones were, a wolf came to flour,
for me, a ticket, they are not renunciation, you should
be a place with a door, if you find a cave
with a door, I'm like, why did you previously think
that caves were something more sacred, no,
it's just annoying, you should be, I
like to talk, I like small ones, I
thought, and but I want him to be, or
heads, why, and centuries-old ones, I hate
drama, I don't want to die, I don't want a house with
five rooms,
he offered me, I don't pressure him with alcohol, and
you know his name, I said no, I don't want him, he
keeps asking me about them and
says, I built you a dahmer, I don't want a
house that needs to be
cleaned and tidied up all the time, and I want my little
elegant, powerful house, Chris's house, Paul,
calm to a small eye, Clivie  Less
cleaning
and this renunciation, you can have a beautiful house,
no problem,
this is not denial. Cancer treatment,
you can have a good job, a good
long time, TASS yogis and they allow
yogis to be in my house. Why? Because
they listen to the whole refrigerator, these are all
always on your couch.
You go to work to get the sofa right,
and then an empty refrigerator when you
come back. I don't want you to be
such yogis. Having reported, a teacher is a homeless person, this
is a waste of time. Earn money,
be responsible. That's it. I
made a list of the best teachers and
they are all responsible people. Some
of them have families. Some of them
have good jobs. They own large
companies. There is a decline, but they are responsible. You see, yes,
I would say this is one of the
most important. The devil is in the details. I want to. I won't
trust you with my life if you can't feed yourself.
Zimin, I understand, sacrifices. I won't trust you with
my spiritual sacrifices
if you can't figure out how to
earn 50 grams of
dollars a day. You understand, the second,
first main path, you can call it
renunciation, too, I don't want to edit all the
answers. Gasoline, what does this mean? I
began to see suffering in this world.  I'm
tired of this, I'm tired, I don't want this anymore,
these wars in Syria, in Israel, a
friend, they are in demand by anyone. A few
days ago, I'm tired of this, of seeing, I'm
tired of all this madness and OST, I'm
tired of people dying all the time
around me, I'm tired of this,
guys, this is the first
example, the main path, what will you write in your
homework? I'm tired, I don't want this anymore, I don't
want people around me to not die,
my elderly grandmother is so lonely, I
suffer in that it's the last, everyone
died around her, there's no one to call, and this will happen to
us, it will happen to you, the
day will come when the last
person dies, from this group of these
cookies, I'm tired and I want to see this, I
want this, this is the first main path. I'm tired.
If you want to show your level of
English, you can write a renunciation, but
I'm tired of these words, let's
just write, I'm tired.
There are planets, you need to fix it, from the ass, where
this cube of m has already stopped
history, from the whole planet, where people, all
people are from tea, thousands, and no one
dies anymore, no one meets
annoying, irritable people, everyone is so
happy here because they understand,
and every planet passes.  I've been
messing around with this, some have already finished, some in the
middle, some aren't there at all, I will be this is the
first, the first main path, the second
main path, who to get sick from is called
the accounts.
If you see a book on which it
is written, you will have a translation of the word
bodhichitta, throw it away.
They don't know what they are talking about. People aren't
often given books at the Volga airport. Here's a
book for you.
I'm passing through the border on the other side, I
throw away this book,
especially if it says that Buddha or the
enlightened one are
ready. This means the desire for
enlightenment. This doesn't mean I just
glanced. It's
important that they are already enlightened, and you must
receive it. To achieve this in Dota, the wagon will
remain. I want to become
enlightened
so that I can divide the number of things into two and
help many people from the suffering from
which I already have because this is natural.
I got confused. I'm tired of what to do with
this. I'll insert nonsense until I can
make many bodies and I can teach
and on 7 billion different planets. If you want to
do this in one country over
the Internet, the desire for enlightenment.
I write above desire with a capital letter, that
is, a capital letter. The desire will be this
gathering, it does not mean enlightened. This is a
very bad translation.
Super bad James Ransone
super swim teeth and this is a super graph
you see this doesn't mean this at all
if you look at this you will see this the whole book is
bad Kyiv
even though the translation is ninety percent of
my
irritation remained the project The Word just
kidding 3 main let's go and violently if you
want to become a Buddha to help all
beings then you must see
emptiness directly and this is the third way
want to call it wise than in
English wisdom means a wise
person does not drive a car too fast
does not eat EDS cholesterol much
wisdom and we are not talking about this wisdom
we are talking about
saw then simply directly or not you
can become such a person if you
follow this activity this
torment if you do the meditations
that you are here with with which you are
studying here you can become Aryans you leaders
join
as on pride and posture virgins you have
everything you need and every
person in this room has access to
direct perception of emptiness
and most people in the sky room do not have
this reason so that frankly you
have everything you need to see
instead of 1 for example if  you will see this
ndsm and he - at that very same hour you
will see all the planets, every planet and
every person on this planet and you
will experience
intense love for every creature during
this for hours and then after that for the
rest of your life, nothing
will bother you, how can yours, what after
this, calm, I like what you're
cooking for dinner, dude, I've seen so many
creatures, calm, I don't care what you
think about my dinner, it's
almost practically impossible, is
n't it a theory, what does it say? If you
saw your own,
you saw the day when you will become
enlightened and you know that who in general
only if the address will be very
difficult, but this is so that and mom, it's
worth doing the entire SEO course
to see the emptiness directly so that no
one ever
angers or irritates you again. You can do
this experience that happens immediately after
you see, I'll put another one at the same
hour,
nothing compares to this, what
happens an hour before the direct perception of
the post, you give me an exact answer, mustache, you
see how the seed opens in your
own consciousness for the first time in your life,
language,
school, only you see how the storage
closes itself, you see it's always like this,
technically
an hour before you see and emptiness here is the
fish for the first time
you see what is happening with this computer
Your seeds are produced
from you and also who will anger you after
that, your husband who yells at you,
there is also something happening to you if you
want to punish someone, show yourself, you
understand, this also happens, you
will see dependent origination an hour
before you had grams of perception
in the top, I put it because dependent
origination means that all things, how many
of you, why can't you, people,
I am the words of Michael, he has been
teaching you for so many years, why don't you see this on earth, you still don't
see that it is too
fast,
65 seeds per second, you need to
meditate and you need good
meditation to see this, good, these are the
three main ones, be and let's do a review. 1.
I'm tired of amara.org.
2. I want to be a Buddha
to help myself, the whole universe. I'm
finishing this week on this
planet, I need to be finished by Sunday, and
then I treated another planet,
this is such a tower, you can say
desire with a capital letter. By the way, I
answered, did,
wrote the answer and there are 6 pages of homework. 3. The
main one is they call it
direct perception of emptiness in Russian, it would be
PVP, this is the first course, what the
first course is about. 10  This is the main subject of the first
year and everything will be covered in the
first year. I went, why then all the
other courses? I don't know. It will turn out to be cool. The last question of the homework. There
will be no break. If you need to say this,
just go out. I allow it. Has a
snack.
The lights are
killing. The last question is
these three main paths. Is it mental,
physical, or is this concept?
Are these mental things? Are these relationships? These are not
paths. This is not how it even is. Leru, in
Celsius, this is not in the morning.
This is an idea. A tooth, tenge, a way of thinking.
Most likely, they should have been named. Three
main relationships. In the following ones,
a call comes from ours. I finished my homework. I am
absolutely sure that it will pass. Sorry, there is no
microphone. Three problems with
the vessel. The first is that you are not open, you are
inverted. The second is that you hear. You
mix
Silas K and shamans, and so on with
others. Jeremy 3. Becky. You penetrate. I was walking. The
struggle gives you something. You
forget it. By tomorrow, you
understand. You don't hold it or retain it
for teaching. Author 2.